ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Brief of ILGWU in the Matter of the California Sportswear and Dress Association, Inc., et al. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume I. (Box 8, Folder 14a)
  Table of Contents, Formal Pleadings, Briefs, Orders, etc. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume II. (Box 8, Folder 14b)
  Briefs for ILGWU, et al. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume III. (Box 8, Folder 14c)
  Transcript of Testimony pgs. 1-692. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume IV. (Box 8, Folder 14d)
  Transcript of Testimony pgs. 693-1165. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). National Association of Blouse Manufacturers., 1943-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  10/43-12/60. Related case.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume V. (Box 9, Folder 1a)
  List of Commission's Exhibits and Commission's Exhibits. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume VI. (Box 9, Folder 1b)
  List of Respondents' Exhibits and Respondents' Exhibits 1-20. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume VII. (Box 9, Folder 1c)
  Respondents' Exhibits 21-A--R to 58-A--2-82. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Case File. Volume VIII. (Box 9, Folder 1d)
  Respondents' Exhibit 3. 1 bound volume.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  5/41-4/51. Related case.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Miscellaneous., 1939-1954 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  5/39-8/54.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Miscellaneous., 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  1955-2/58.
- Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear). Miscellaneous. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Undated.
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR). Correspondence about election case. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  12/60-4/63.
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR). Correspondence about election case. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- FOUR. Correspondence and materials regarding challenged ballots in election case. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 1)
- FOUR. Correspondence and materials regarding challenged ballots in election case. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 2)
- FOUR. Payroll schedules used to determine the appropriate composition of the bargaining unit. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- FOUR. Legal documents, decisions in election case. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  12/60-8/62.
- FOUR. Legal documents, decisions in election case. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- FOUR. Summary of testimony in election case., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  1/61-2/61.
- FOUR. Correspondence and documents about the refusal to bargain case. [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  4/61-11/63.
- FOUR. Correspondence and documents about the refusal to bargain case. [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- FOUR. Correspondence regarding alleged unfair labor practices. [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  3/61-8/65.
- FOUR. Correspondence regarding alleged unfair labor practices. [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- FOUR. Correspondence regarding alleged unfair labor practices. [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- FOUR. Correspondence regarding discharges of Mike Gross and Pat Levenstein., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  2/61-10/61.
- FOUR. Affidavits regarding unfair labor practices case. (Box 10, Folder 12a)
- FOUR. Research (Precedents, agreements, notes, etc.). (Box 10, Folder 13)
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding unfair labor practices case. [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  3/61-5/63. Complaints, answers, motions, decisions, etc.
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding unfair labor practices case. [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding unfair labor practices case. [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- FOUR. Summary of witness testimony in unfair labor practices case. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  pgs. 144-2039.
- FOUR. Summary of witness testimony in unfair labor practices case. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  pgs. 2044-4000.
- FOUR. Summary of witness testimony in unfair labor practices case. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  pgs. 4000-4707.
- FOUR. General Counsel's exhibits in unfair labor practices cases. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- FOUR. Respondent's exhibits in unfair labor practices cases. (Box 11, Folder 3a)
- FOUR. Respondent's rejected exhibits in unfair labor practices cases. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- FOUR. Correspondence about U.S. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  5/63-5/66.
- FOUR. Correspondence about U.S. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding U.S. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  5/63-4/66. Petitions, answers, motions, memoranda, decisions, etc.
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding U.S. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- FOUR. Legal documents regarding U.S. Court of Appeals cases. [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- FOUR. Propaganda and newsletters by staff union, editorials., 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  3/61-2/64.
- FOUR. Newspaper clippings, ILGWU propaganda., 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  12/60-9/63.
- FOUR. Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Gantner and Mattern Company. (Box 11, Folder 12a)
  1 bound volume. Contains: Opening Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, on Motion to Quash Alleged Service of Summons.; Brief Replying to Opening Brief of Defendant International Ladies' Garment Workers Union and Opening Brief of Knitgood Workers' Union Local 191.; Reply Brief of Defendant, International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, on Motion to Quash Alleged Service of Summons.; Petition for Writ of Prohibition.; Brief and Points and Authorities in Support of Petition for Writ of Prohibition.; Petition for a Rehearing.; Petition for a Hearing by the Supreme Court.; Respondents' Answer to Petition for a Hearing by the Supreme Court.; Petition for Writ of Certiorari.; Brief for Respondents in Opposition to Petition for Writ of Certiorari.; Reply Brief on Behalf of Petitioners.; Transcript of Record.
- Georgetown Dress Corporation vs. ILGWU., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  4/74-7/74.
- G. S. Supply Associates, Inc. vs. Union Local 20408 of the United Warehouse, Industrial and Affiliate Trades Employees Union. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  10/78-11/78.
- G. S. Supply Associates, Inc. vs. Union Local 20408 of the United Warehouse, Industrial and Affiliate Trades Employees Union. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- G. S. Supply Associates, Inc. vs. Union Local 20408 of the United Warehouse, Industrial and Affiliate Trades Employees Union., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  11/78.
- Hazantown. Correspondence of Emil Schlesinger and Max Zimny., 1973-1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  11/73-1/78.
- Hazantown. Sample jobber agreements. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Hazantown. Legal documents. [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  10/73-8/74.
- Hazantown. Legal documents. [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Hazantown. Legal documents. [folder 3 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Horenson vs. Kramarsky., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  6/80.
- Immigration and Naturalization Service vs. Delgado., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  3/81-11/81. Brief and Reply Brief of ILGWU in U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals Case.
- Immigration and Naturalization Service vs. Delgado. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Brief in Opposition to the Petition for Writ of Certiorari; Joint Appendix; Brief for the Petitioner.
- Immigration and Naturalization Service vs. Delgado. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Brief for Respondents; Reply Brief for Petitioners; Briefs for Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund, American Jewish Committee, and American Civil Liberties Union.
- Jou Designs, et al. vs. ILGWU., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Judy Bond. General Correspondence. [folder 1 of 3], 1961-19/6 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  9/61-10/66. Morris Glushien, Elias Lieberman, David Dubinsky, Max Zimny and Others.
- Judy Bond. General Correspondence. [folder 2 of 3], 1961-19/6 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Judy Bond. General Correspondence. [folder 3 of 3], 1961-19/6 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-19/6 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  1/62-11/66. About run-away shop charges vs. company, back pay for northern contract workers.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-19/6 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 12, Folder 17)
  About dispute between ILGWU and United Garment Workers of America (UGW) over UGW's contract at Brewton plant.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  3/62-5/68. About unfair labor practices committed jointly by company and UGW.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence and materials. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  1/62-4/64. Concerning arbitration awards and court cases.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence and materials. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence and materials., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  5/63-11/64. About secondary boycott charges filed against ILGWU.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  3/64-6/64. About unfair labor practice charges filed by company against ILGWU.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  2/65-10/66. About unfair labor practice charges filed by ILGWU against company.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  6/66-9/69. About compliance by company with retirement and back pay orders.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Judy Bond. Internal company correspondence., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  4/64.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  2/62-12/65. About campaign against the company.
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Judy Bond. Correspondence. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Judy Bond. Newspaper clippings., 1961-1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  12/61-1/69.
- Judy Bond. Emporium Capwell., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  10/63-5/64. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Greenwood Shirt Company., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  3/62-5/62. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Hartley vs. ILGWU., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  5/66. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Iva Manufacturing Company. Correspondence. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  1/62-4/64. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Iva Manufacturing Company. Correspondence. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Judy Bond. Iva Manufacturing Company. Correspondence. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Judy Bond. Iva Manufacturing Company. Legal documents. (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Judy Bond. Jamel Inc. Correspondence about South Carolina court cases., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  1/62-8/62. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Jamel Inc. Correspondence about National Labor Relations Board cases. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  2/60-6/63. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Jamel Inc. Correspondence about National Labor Relations Board cases. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Judy Bond. Jamel Inc. Newspaper clippings., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  1/62-9/62. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Montgomery Ward., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  8/63-2/64. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Nat Nast Inc., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  5/64-8/64. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Ozark Manufacturing Company., 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  1961-12/66. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Pomeroy's Department Store., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  8/64-10/64. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Sivley vs. ILGWU., 1962-1966 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  3/62-5/66. Related case.
- Judy Bond. Miscellaneous., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  Employees' names, addresses, and wages for Well Made Novelty Company and Cardinal Blouse Company.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  1/66-10/66.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  11/66.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  12/66.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  1/67-2/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  3/67-6/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  6/67-7/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  8/67-11/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  12/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  1/68.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  2/68-6/68.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  7/68-12/68.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  1/69-2/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  3/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  4/69-12/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). General Correspondence., 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  8/70-4/72.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Election case at Oppenheimer plant (26-RC-2533)., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  10/65-4/66.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Election case at Oppenheimer plant. Company and union propaganda., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  8/65-10/65.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Election case at Oppenheimer plant. Company and union propaganda., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  10/65-12/65
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Election case at Oppenheimer plant. Company and union propaganda., 1965-1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  12/65-4/76.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-2313., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  9/65-10/66. Alleged discriminatory discharge and layoffs of workers, threats, interrogations, invalid company rules. Settled.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-2641 and 26-CA-2721., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  12/66-4/67. Alleged company refusal to bargain - includes affidavits of James Youngdahl, Frederick Siems, George Lambert, and John P. Sizemore.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-2641 and 26-CA-2721 continued., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  5/67-12/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-2641 and 26-CA-2721 continued., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  12/67. Issuance of complaint in 26-CA-2313 (violation of settlement), filing of charge 26-CA-2952 (alleged company refusal to bargain), orders consolidating all 4 cases (referred to as Big NLRB case).
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  12/67-1/68. Includes motions by company for extension of time to plead and dismissals of complaints.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  1/68. Includes roster of striking employees.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  1/68-3/68. Includes subpoenas, order denying company motion to dismiss complaints.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Brief On Behalf of the General Counsel., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  4/19/68.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Respondent's Brief to the Trial Examiner., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Charging Party's Exceptions and Brief., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  4/20/68.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Charging Party's Brief., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  4/68-10/68. Includes General Counsel's Motion to Amend Consolidated Complaint.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Order Transferring Case to the National Labor Relations Board., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  1/28/69. Includes Trial Examiner's decision.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  1/69-3/69. Includes Respondent's Motion to Re-Open the Record.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Respondent's Exceptions to Trial Examiner's Decision., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  3/12/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  3/69. Includes Respondent's Brief in Support of Exceptions to the Trial Examiner's Decision.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Big NLRB case. Correspondence., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  3/69-9/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). U.S. Court of Appeals cases 19,858 and 19,982 (Big NLRB case on appeal). Correspondence., 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  6/69-11/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). U.S. Court of Appeals cases 19,858 and 19,982 (Big NLRB case on appeal). Correspondence., 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  11/69-12/70.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). U.S. Supreme Court case 1291 (Big NLRB case on appeal)., 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  12/70-4/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  2/71-12/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  1/72-3/72.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  4/72-12/72.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  1/73-12/73.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  1/74-6/74. Includes union's Request for Review by the General Counsel.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  7/74-12/74. Includes chronology of the case, gross backpay computation.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  1/75. Includes request by union to modify government's selection of witnesses.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  5/75-9/75. Includes company's Special Appeal from Law Judge's Rulings During Conduct of Backpay Proceedings, settlement proposals.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Correspondence regarding company's compliance with ruling on Big NLRB case., 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  10/75- 1/78. Includes union's agreement to settle with company.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing in Big NLRB case to enforce company's compliance. [folder 1 of 3], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  5/21/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing in Big NLRB case to enforce company's compliance. [folder 2 of 3], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing in Big NLRB case to enforce company's compliance. [folder 3 of 3], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 1 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 2 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 3 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 4 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 4 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Appendices to Back pay Specification and Notice of Hearing. [folder 6 of 6], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board in the Matter of: Kellwood Company and International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, AFL-CIO Docket No. 26-CA-2313, 26-CA- 2641, 26-CA-2721, 26-CA-2952 (Big NLR, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  10/3/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 4., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  10/4/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 5., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  10/8/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 6., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  10/9/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 10., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  11/6/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 11., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  11/7/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 12., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  11/8/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 13., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  11/11/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 18., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  1/7/75.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 19., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  1/8/75.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 20., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  1/9/75.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 21., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  1/10/75.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Official Report of Proceedings (Big NLRB case). Volume 22., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  1/20/75.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Cases related to unemployment compensation claims of unfair labor practice strikers and workers fired by company., 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  10/65-4/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-2533 and 26-CA-2612., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  2/67-4/67. Alleged unfair discharge of Mary Bearden, grants of wage increases to avoid unionization, interrogations of employees, solicitation of employees to engage in surveillance of union activities. Charges concern activities at plant in Lonoke, Arkansas.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). U.S. Court of Appeals (8th Circuit) cases 19,295 and 19,364., 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  6/68-9/69. Appeals of NLRB cases 26-CA-2533 and 26-CA-2612 (Lonoke, Arkansas plant).
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Kellwood Company vs. George Lambert, et al., Chancery Court of Pulaski, Arkansas No. 134761 and related cases. [folder 1 of 3], 1966- 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  10/66-1/68. Injunction against union picketing, appeal to Arkansas Supreme Court.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Kellwood Company vs. George Lambert, et al., Chancery Court of Pulaski, Arkansas No. 134761 and related cases. [folder 2 of 3], 1966- 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Kellwood Company vs. George Lambert, et al., Chancery Court of Pulaski, Arkansas No. 134761 and related cases. [folder 3 of 3], 1966- 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Dorothy Kaufman vs. Marilyn Eaves and Ottenheimer Brothers Manufacturing Company., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)